freeflysystems.com 2017-11-03

# Privacy Policy - Freefly Systems

By using the Freefly Systems (“Freefly”) website (freeflysystems.com) and/or any of Freefly’s online or mobile products or services, Freefly hardware or software, or other services (“Services”), including when you access the Services through mobile devices, you agree to Freefly’s Privacy Policy and that we may transfer and store your information in the United States. Any personal information that you provide to Freefly is used for the purpose of receiving Freefly communications and for personalizing and enhancing your web experience with Freefly. Freefly’s Privacy Policy is outlined below and tells you how we collect personal information, what information we collect, how we use it, how we share it, and how you can access, change and remove your information.

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SERVICES. We will post any modifications or changes to the Privacy Policy on the Freefly website. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so we encourage you to review it frequently.  Your continued use of the Services signifies your acceptance of our Privacy Policy as modified.

## HOW WE COLLECT THE INFORMATION

Freefly collects both personal information and non-personal information that you provide to us. Freefly may obtain information from you through: (i) account registration and administration of your account through the Freefly website, online store and/or forum; (ii) online, email or telephone purchases; (iii) customer service and technical support; (iv) newsletter subscriptions; (v) navigational information about where visitors go on our website; (vi) contest registration and prize acceptance; (vii) registering your Freefly products; (viii) providing updates to you about your Freefly products; (ix) access to Freefly products or services on social networks or third party services; and (x) other uses of the Services where personal information is requested for use and or/participation. This information may be collected by Freefly or by service providers retained by Freefly and obligated to maintain your personal information in a confidential manner.  

## INFORMATION WE COLLECT

The types of personal and non-personal information collected will depend upon the activity and may include your full name, email address, phone number, address, credit card information, professional title, birth date, or product serial number. Freefly contest winners may be required to provide their social security number and other information for tax purposes, which will only be used for prize fulfillment purposes.

When you use Freefly’s Services that connect to the internet, we may collect certain information as described below for such purposes as providing and improving our products and software services, tracking usage, troubleshooting bugs, providing content for referring traffic sources and improving overall performance of the Services.  Such information may include IP address, browser type, profile information, preferences, aggregate user data, technical session information, information about your computer, hardware, software, or mobile device, including a device identifier, demographic information including gender, zip code and age, and navigational data.  User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes. If you arrived at our website via a link from another webpage, we may receive aggregate or otherwise anonymous statistical information about your visit to our site. We monitor visitor site usage and traffic patterns to help us develop the design and layout of the site, and to improve the content of our website to better match the interests of our website visitors.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small removable data file that is stored by your web browser on your computer hard drive. Freefly uses cookies to store website visitors’ preferences and to record visit information, such as pages visited, time spent on the website, interactions with website features, shopping cart items, and purchase behavior for various purposes such as ensuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements, to tailor website content and newsletter communications according to visitor preferences, to serve online advertisements based on past visits to the website, and to inform and optimize website performance and online advertising campaigns. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personal Information you submit to us.

Freefly allows third parties to collect non-personal information by way of cookies, web beacons, and as described below from the Freefly website.  Freefly does not enable third parties to collect any personal information directly from the Services for their own promotional purposes.  You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set through your browser settings. However, by deleting or disabling cookies, you may not be able to access certain areas or features of the website.  

### Web Beacons

Web beacons are tiny graphics with a unique identifier that are used to track the online movements of web users. While cookies are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded on web pages and are typically the size of a pixel. One or more of our marketing partners uses web beacons to help us better manage content on our site by informing us as to what content is effective.  

### Ad Servers, Third Party Advertising, and Website Analytics

Freefly works with website analytics and advertising partners, including Google, Quantcast and Facebook, to deliver Freefly advertisements on third party publisher websites, and these partners may set cookies on your computer’s web browser. These cookies allow our partners to recognize your computer so that the ad server can show you Freefly advertisements elsewhere on the Internet, and so that our analytics software can measure your engagement and interactions while using freeflysystems.com.  As a result, ad servers may compile anonymous, non-personal information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw our advertisements, whether or not you interacted with our advertisements and actions performed on subsequent visits to freeflysystems.com. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you, and it allows Freefly to optimize the performance of our advertising campaigns and the usability of our website.  

### Information from Other Sources

Freefly may receive information about you from third parties, such as commerce partners, marketers, social network services, and other parties that we may use to supplement the information that we collect directly from you.  If you connect to a third party network, platform, or service through the Services, you are authorizing us to collect, store, and use in accordance with this Privacy Policy any and all information that you agreed the social network or other third party platform could provide to Freefly based on your settings on the third party social network or platform.  Your agreement takes place when you connect with the third party network, platform, or service via our Services, and/or when you connect with one of our applications through one of these services.  

## HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION

By providing us with your personal information, you consent to us processing this personal information in one or more of the ways described in this Privacy Policy.

Freefly may use non-personal information to improve performance of our Services, to understand how anonymous users interact with our website after seeing Freefly advertisements, to identify and retarget advertisements to past website visitors, and to optimize the performance of our advertising campaigns.

Freefly may use both non-personal information and personal information to enable the purchase and fulfillment of Freefly products and services, and to improve the overall Freefly customer and product experience.

We will primarily use your personal information to provide products and services to you, for example:

  * To fulfill your order and follow-up with customer satisfaction emails. The information we ask for when you order online is used to complete the order, confirm the order and to confirm shipment of the order.
  * To provide customer service and technical support and manage your account.
  * To send you information about products, offers and news we think could interest you. We only send you this if you have opted-in to receive such notifications.
  * To administer a giveaway, promotion, survey or other site feature and to provide you with the relevant products or services.
  * To send service-related announcements when necessary to do so. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature.
  * To analyze visits to our website and learn about the interests of our visitors in the aggregate and to better understand your personal interests and needs, so we can improve our products and services.

## SHARING INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES

Freefly does not share, sell, or rent to other third parties for their own promotional purposes any personal information you provide to us, and will only share personal Information as outlined below or with your consent.

### Third Party Service Providers

We use other third party service providers to offer or facilitate services on our behalf, such as payment processing and authorization, fraud protections and credit risk reduction, order fulfillment and shipping, marketing and promotional material distribution, website evaluation and data analysis. We may need to share personal information with these third parties so that they can perform these services, however, we limit the personal information that we give to them and authorize them to use this information only for the purpose of performing those services.  

### Facebook Custom Audience Ads

We may display interest-based ads to you when you are using Facebook through Facebook’s Custom Audience Tool. The Custom Audience Tool allows us to personalize our ads based on your shopping experience with us. We do not share any of your personal information or your shopping history with Facebook. This tool allows us to convert your email address to a unique number that Facebook uses to match to unique numbers that Facebook generates from email addresses of its users. You may opt-out of Facebook Custom Audience ads from Freefly by emailing [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#442925362f21302d2a23042236212122283d373d37302129376a272b297b3731262e2127307902252721262b2b2f64073137302b29640531202d212a272164052037X%20Opt-Out) with this request.  

### Customer Testimonials

We may post customer testimonials on our website which may contain personal information. We will obtain your consent via email and/or opt-in methods prior to posting your name, city, or stated activity/interest along with any testimonial.  

### User-Generated Content

You may be able to disclose information about yourself in the course of contributing user generated content on publicly-available areas of the Services.  Such information is unencrypted, public information, may be accessed or recorded by us, and there is no expectation of privacy or confidentiality in such information. Any personal information you submit in the course of such activities can be read, collected, or used by other users.

If you submit your video or other content to Freefly, we may publish it on the Freefly website, social media channels, or applications along with certain personal information identifying you, such as your first and last name or your username, when we have your consent.  

### Legal Compliance

We reserve the right to access and disclose your personal information when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to: (i) enforce legal rights and comply with the law; (ii) comply with an order from a government entity or other competent authority, (iii) prevent or address potential or actual injury or interference with our rights, property, operations, users or others who may be harmed or may suffer loss or damage; or (iv) protect our rights, prevent fraud and/or comply with judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on Freefly.  

### Business Transactions

As with any business, it is possible that as our business develops, we might go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or a sale of all or a portion of our assets.  Information that we collect, including your personal and non-personal information, is considered a business asset and will likely be disclosed or transferred to a third party acquirer in connection with the transaction.  

## THIRD PARTY WEBSITES

Freefly’s Services may contain links to or features from other websites. This Privacy Policy covers the privacy practices by Freefly, and does not cover the privacy practices of third party websites or features. Freefly is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices of third parties. When linking to another website or using a third party service, you should read the privacy policy on that website or service.  

## HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION

The security of your personal information is important to us.  We have implemented reasonable administrative, technical, and physical security measures to protect against the unauthorized access, destruction or alteration of your information.  We use industry standard SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption during the order check-out process to protect the confidentiality of your personal information. Despite our best efforts, however, no security measures are completely impenetrable.  

## INTERNATIONAL USERS

Freefly operates in the United States and, as a result, the information we collect may be stored in the United States. Your personal information may be transferred to, used, processed, or held by Freefly in the United States and in other countries, including countries outside of your country of residence, and used for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy.  

## CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

Freefly’s Services are intended for general audiences and not for children under the age of 14. If you are under 14, you should visit the Freefly website and forum only with the involvement of a parent or legal guardian. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 14, and if we become aware of such collection, we will take reasonable steps to delete such information as soon as practicable.  

## CORRECTING / UPDATING OR REMOVING INFORMATION

Freefly users may modify or remove any of their personal information collected by Freefly at any time by logging into their account. Users may also email us to correct or change any information by contacting Customer Support at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  

## OPT OUT / UNSUBSCRIBE

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and other communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#e794929797889593a781958282818b9e949e9493828a94c984888a). If you want to opt-out from receiving communications from any third party that is not our agent or service provider, please contact that third party directly.  

## FREEFLY CONTACT INFORMATION

Freefly Systems Inc.  
15540 Woodinville-Redmond Rd NE  
Bldg A, Ste 800  
Woodinville, WA 98072  

## UPDATES TO PRIVACY INFORMATION

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy on our website so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently.

_This Privacy Policy was last updated on December  4, 2015._
